{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110058893","data":{"timestamp":" 947110058893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110066330","data":{"timestamp":" 947110066330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110093507","data":{"timestamp":" 947110093507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110101046","data":{"timestamp":" 947110101046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110109416","data":{"timestamp":" 947110109416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110118239","data":{"timestamp":" 947110118239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110130471","data":{"timestamp":" 947110130471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110147373","data":{"timestamp":" 947110147373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110157360","data":{"timestamp":" 947110157360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947110174560","data":{"timestamp":" 947110174560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_010701"," gameId":" 861b9899-b917-4a8b-9ce2-fd7db7f45325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.wa.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"end":"end"}]}